OUSSAMA BACHA | TEACHER

Sidi slimane, Tissemsilt, Algeria | 06 58 23 51 55 | 38028 Tissemsilt oussama.bacha.etu@univ-mosta.dz

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Mr. Oussama is currently working as Teacher In Mathematics in Secondary school , Tissemsilt, Algeria. Mr. Oussama is doing research In Complex Analysis and asymptotic distribution of values of a meromorphic function "Nevanlinna theory" , respectively, Study of the order and the hyper-order of some differential equations in the complex domain

| | | SKILLS |
|--|--|------------------------------------|
| Real and complex analysis | | ✓ Entire and meromorphic functions |
| Mathematical analysis | | Differential equations |
| Complex differential equations | | Functional analysis |
| ✓ Nevanlinna theory | | ✓ Integration |
| | | |

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1st International Conference on Frontiers in Academic Research

Konya - Turkey | 18 February, 2023 - 21 February, 2023

 Peper title "On The Growth of Solutions of Certain Second-Order Linear Differential Equations".

2nd International Conference on Innovative Academic Studies

Konya - Turkey | 28 January, 2023 - 31 January, 2023

Peper title "On meromorphic solutions of second - order linear differential equations".

1st International Conference on Engineering, Natural and Social Sciences

Konya - Turkey | 20 December, 2022 - 23 December, 2022

• Peper title "Solutions to a class of linear differential equations increase locally and oscillate close to a singular point".

1st International Conference on Engineering, Natural and Social Sciences

Konya - Turkey | 20 December, 2022 - 23 December, 2022

• Peper title "Growth of solutions to linear differential equations with analytic coefficients near a punctured disk".

COURSES AND PROJECTS

Latex

Tissemsilt, Algeria | 15 March, 2019 - 28 October, 2019

- Learn about different packages and commands.
- Learn how to edit texts in English

Geogebra

Tissemsilt, Algeria 07 March, 2018 - 29 September, 2018

- Learn how to draw various geometric shapes and curves
- Learn many skills and link them with Latak

EDUCATION

Mar 2020 - Nov 2022 | Abdelhamid Ibn Badis University in Mostaganem, Algeria

2nd registration in doctorate in Mathematics - mathematical analysis Thesis title "Results on complex delay-differential equations".

Nov 2018 - jul 2019 | university of chlef, Algeria

Master in Mathematics - scientific modeling and computing

Thesis title "Explicit solution of first and second order hyperbolic problems".

sep 2012 - jun 2017 | Higher School of Teachers in Laghouat, Algeria

State engineer in mathematics - Mathematics

Thesis title "Solve some problems of partial differential equations using the finite element method".

sep 2011 - jun 2012 | Boucaid secondary school-Tissemsilt, Algeria

Bachelor in Mathematics - Mathematical Technologist

LANGUAGES

Arabic: native English: b1 French: b1